Hello and welcome friends, all of you are welcome
to Traders Channel.  If you all found it a bit
informative and knowledgeable, then
please like, share and subscribe to the channel,
friends.  So let us discuss which
stocks are going to give their quarter four results in the month of April.
Let us see, the stock of Anand Rathi
company will come on 9th April, that
of JB Re will come on 9th April, that means the
stock of RSL will also come today, the
stock of TCS which all the people are waiting to
see, its stock is
also coming today and Agritech will also
come on 10th April.  Eco Hotels will also
arrive on 10th April i.e. tomorrow.  Ok let's go.
Next let's see our our
worship
worship on on on 10th April.  Look friends,
our stock of Pujan will arrive on 10th April.
Our AQ loan will come on 11th April.
B2B Shopt will arrive on April 11.  So
GSP Crop will come on 11th April, Swaad Tour will come on
11th April and Urvi Def will also come on 11th
April, we will know the result of all these stocks on
11th April.  Now we
see Pakun arriving on April 13th.
ICICI AMC will announce its quarter four result on 13th April, sorry
friends, Ind Bank
will also announce its quarter four result on 30th April.
Innovision will also announce its quarter four results on April 13.
Just Dial will also be on
April 13.  Quarter for result
announced and Swaraj
ENG that too quarter four result will be announced on 13th April.  Let's see.
DEN's quarter four results will also be announced on April 14.
Imiko
Im Imicoleko Immicoleko will also be on April 14.
Hey, that too will be on April 14th.  ICIC
Rule Sorry friends, ICIC PIULI will come
on 14th April, Kapil Vaz will also come on 14th April,
NUV NUVCO will also come on 14th April, its
quarter four result will come on 14th April, ok Surya Chakra on 14th April,
Ekan on 15th April, GTPL on 15th April,
HDBF stock will also
come on 15th April, ICICGI will come on 15th April, Nikki
ICL will also announce quarter four result on 15th April.
RIIL's
quarter four results will be announced on April 15.
SPLS quarter four
result will be announced on 15th April.  Tulsi's
quarter four results will also be announced on April 15.
Our company One is also going to disclose
its quarter four results on April 16.
CRISIL HDFC
AMC is going to disclose its quarter four results on April 16.
Let's
see what's next.  Next HDFC
L is going to disclose its quarter four results on 16th April.
I visited
Wipro
or
sorry friends Wipro, all of them are going to
disclose their quarter 4 results on 16th April.
Both Heath Mastercard and these companies are going to
announce their quarter four results on April 17.  If
you all find this video
a little informative and valuable, then
please like, share and subscribe to the channel,
friends.  Look at the
banks on April 18, HDFC Bank, ICICI
Bank and Yes Bank are the three banks which are going to disclose
their quarter four results on April 18.
PNB Housing on
April 20 SML MA on April 20 These are all the
stocks that are
awaited.  This means that a
very great move is about to happen in Bank Nifty, friends.
Sign TDLM on 21st April HCL Tech is going to
disclose quarter four result on 21st April.
National Int Resistant on April 21
AML Quarter Four Result is going to be announced on April 21.
Haves
Quarter 4 results will
come on 22nd April LTDS Quarter
results will come on 22nd April Maha Scooter
Tech on 22nd April Adanisold
Quarter 4 results are going to be disclosed on 23rd April.
Infie LTMK
Tata CF UTI
AMC All these companies are going to
disclose their quarter 44 results on 23rd April.
Adanri is our important stock,
Adan's quarter 4 result is going to come on 24th April,
ok let's go,
next is coming, Atul, on 24th April the
quarter four result is going to be disclosed,
Indus
Indus Bank IDFC FST Bank Ind SBFC
sorry friends, Atul, on 24th April the
quarter four result is going to be disclosed, Indus In Bank on 24th April.
India
sorry friends IDFC FS Bank India Cam is going to be
disclosed on 25th April.
SBFC is going to be disclosed on 25th April.
Quarter 4 Results ATCL on 27th April,
keep an eye on all these stocks, friends,
and subscribe to the channel.  So you will keep getting updates on the
quarter 4 results of all these stocks.
Bajaj HFL 27
April CR AMO 27 April MA RL 27
April NM India 27 April TMB
Ultra CM CO All these
companies are going to disclose their quarter 4 results on 27 April.
Friends,
see, Castleland
Seat LTD is going to disclose its quarter 4 results on 28th April, ML on
28th April, Adan Power on 29th April and
Bajaj Finance on 29th April.
Let's move on to which
companies are coming next?
Capital SFb 29th April Bank 29th April
HG
KTech
MSES
Naveen Floors All these stocks
will announce their quarter four results on 29th April
friends let's go NDTV Bajaj sorry friends
NDTV will be on 29th April Bajaj Fins
Start on 10th April Cholfin
God Agro Room Hindu Hindu & liver
Lalpat Left on 13th April sorry friends
all these stocks are going to be disclosed on 30th April
except NDTV
NDTV is going to be disclosed on 29th April only except NDTV
friends ok if
you all like this information then do
like share and subscribe
friends see you in the next video
I will upload the video of the stock about which the quarter four result will come today
from 6:00 pm so see you all at 6:00 pm till
then take care bye-b